Guide to the Northern Pacific Railway Company Records 1870-1968
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana--Missoula
- Engineering Department, 1870-1968; Subgroup 1; 165.25 linear feet and 14 oversize volumes
  - Rocky Mountain Division (Montana/Idaho), 1882-1961; Series IX; 25.0 linear feet
    - Outgoing Correspondence, George Donald, Missoula, Montana, 1884 (Box-volume 117/166)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, D.M. Driscoll, Cabinet, Montana, 1905 - 1906 (Box-volume 117/167)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, D.M. Driscoll, Cabinet, Montana, 1905 (Box-volume 117/168)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Duke Hunt, Noxon, Montana, 1905 (Box-volume 117/169)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, D.M. Driscoll, Cabinet, Montana, 1905 (Box-volume 117/170)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, D.M. Driscoll, Cabinet, Montana, 1905 (Box-volume 118/171)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, D.M. Driscoll, Cabinet, Montana, 1905 - 1906 (Box-volume 118/172)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, D.M. Driscoll, Cabinet, Montana, 1906 (Box-volume 118/173)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Duke Hunt, Noxon, Montana, 1906 (Box-volume 118/174)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, D.M. Driscoll, Cabinet, Montana, 1906 (Box-volume 118/175)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, C.L. Einley, Noxon, Montana, 1906 - 1907 (Box-volume 118/176)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, D.M. Driscoll, Cabinet, Montana, 1906 (Box-volume 118/177)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, D.M. Driscoll, Cabinet, Montana, 1906 - 1907 (Box-volume 119/178)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, J.C. Bredlove, Paradise, Montana, 1906 (Box-volume 119/179)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, J.C. Bredlove, Paradise, Montana, 1908 (Box-volume 119/180)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Duke Hunt, Noxon, Montana, 1905 (Box-volume 120/181)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, M.J. Ainey, Heron, Idaho, 1905 (Box-volume 120/182)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Duke Hunt, Noxon, Montana, 1905 (Box-volume 120/183)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, D.M. Driscoll, Cabinet, Montana, 1906 (Box-volume 120/184)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, D.M. Driscoll, Cabinet, Montana, 1906 (Box-volume 120/185)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, D.M. Driscoll, Cabinet, Montana, 1906 (Box-volume 120/186)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Duke Hunt, Noxon, Montana, 1905 (Box-volume 120/187)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Duke Hunt, Noxon, Montana, 1906 (Box-volume 120/188)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, D.M. Driscoll, Cabinet, Montana, 1906 (Box-volume 120/189)
    - Financial Records, M.J. Ainey, Noxon, Montana, undated (Box-volume 120/190)
    - Financial Records, C.L. Einely, Noxon, Montana, undated (Box-volume 120/191)
    - Financial Ledger, Noxon, Montana and Hope, Idaho, 1882 - 1883 (Box-volume 120/192)
    - Ledger of Items Shipped, Perma Yard, Idaho, 1882 (Box-volume 120/193)
    - Day Book, 1882 - 1883 (Box-volume 120/194)
    - Financial Records, Bills, 1907 - 1909 (Box-volume 121/195)
    - Invoices, Noxon, Montana, 1905 (Box-volume 121/196)
    - Financial Records, Line Charges, 1905 - 1907 (Box-volume 121/197)
    - Financial Records, Meat Orders, 1906 - 1907 (Box-volume 121/198)
    - Constuction, Horse Plains (Montana) Yard, 1883 - 1884 (Box-volume 121/199)
    - Manifest of Material Shipped or Used, 1883 (Box-volume 122/200)
    - Manifest of Material Shipped or Used, 1883 (Box-volume 122/201)
    - Manifest of Material Shipped or Used, 1883 - 1884 (Box-volume 122/202)
    - Construction Materials, Missoula (Montana) Yard, 1884 (Box-volume 122/203)
    - Construction Materials, Horse Plains (Montana) Yard, 1883 (Box-volume 123/204)
    - Shipping List, 1883 (Box-volume 123/205)
    - Rough Copy of Time Returns, 1883 (Box-volume 123/206)
    - Time Book, M.J. Ainey, 1906 (Box-volume 123/207)
    - Car Report, D.M. Driscoll, 1907 (Box-volume 123/208)
    - Financial Records, Bills, 1905 (Box-volume 123/209)
    - General Correspondence, Boulder Branch, 1932 - 1957 (Box-volume 124/1)
    - General Correspondence, Boulder Branch, 1932 - 1957 (Box-folder 124/2)
    - General Correspondence, Boulder Branch, 1932 - 1957 (Box-folder 124/3)
    - General Correspondence, Bozeman Branch, 1932 - 1957 (Box-folder 124/4)
    - General Correspondence, Bozeman Branch, 1930 - 1965 (Box-folder 124/5)
    - General Correspondence, Camp Creek Branck, 1938 - 1961 (Box-folder 124/6)
    - General Correspondence, Couer d'Alene Branch, 1908 - 1957 (Box-folder 124/7)
    - General Correspondence, Couer d'Alene Branch, 1908 - 1957 (Box-folder 124/8)
    - General Correspondence, Philipsburg Branch, 1919 - 1958 (Box-folder 125/1)
    - General Correspondence, Red Bluffs Branch (Sappington to Harrison/Norris/Pony, Montana), 1934 - 1964 (Box-folder 125/2)
    - General Correspondence, Ruby Valley Branch, 1933 - 1959 (Box-folder 125/3)
    - Boulder Branch Blueprints, undated (Box-folder 125/4)
    - Boulder Branch Blueprints, undated (Box-folder 125/5)
    - Bozeman Branch Blueprints, undated (Box-folder 125/6)
    - Camp Creek Branch Blueprints, undated (Box-folder 126/1)
    - Couer d'Alene Branch Blueprints and Drawings, 1908 - 1957 (Box-folder 126/2)
    - Philipsburg Branch Blueprints, undated (Box-folder 126/3)
    - Red Bluff Branch Blueprints (Sappington to Harrison/Norris/Pony, Montana), undated (Box-folder 126/4)
    - Red Bluff Branch Blueprints (Sappington to Harrison/Norris/Pony, Montana), undated (Box-folder 126/5)
    - Ruby Valley Branch Blueprints, undated (Box-folder 126/6)
    - Correspondence, Missoula-Garrison line (Montana), 1906 - 1907 (Box-folder 127/1)
    - Correspondence, Missoula-Garrison line (Montana), 1908 (Box-folder 127/2)
    - Correspondence, Missoula-Garrison line (Montana), 1908 (Box-folder 127/3)
    - Correspondence, Missoula-Garrison line (Montana), 1908 (Box-folder 127/4)
    - Correspondence, Missoula-Garrison line (Montana), 1908 (Box-folder 127/5)
    - Correspondence, Missoula-Garrison line (Montana), 1908 - 1909 (Box-folder 127/6)
    - Correspondence, Missoula-Garrison line (Montana), 1908 - 1909 (Box-folder 127/7)
    - Correspondence, Missoula-Garrison line (Montana), 1909 (Box-folder 127/8)
    - Correspondence, Missoula-Garrison line (Montana), 1909 (Box-folder 128/1)
    - Correspondence, Missoula-Garrison line (Montana), 1909 (Box-folder 128/2)
    - Correspondence, Missoula-Garrison line (Montana), 1909 (Box-folder 128/3)
    - Correspondence, Missoula-Garrison line (Montana), 1909 (Box-folder 128/4)
    - Correspondence, Missoula-Garrison line (Montana), 1909 (Box-folder 128/5)
    - Correspondence, Missoula-Garrison line (Montana), 1909 (Box-folder 128/6)
    - Correspondence, Missoula-Garrison line (Montana), 1909 (Box-folder 128/7)
    - Correspondence, Missoula-Garrison line (Montana), 1909 - 1910 (Box-folder 129/1)
    - Correspondence, Glendive Montana, 1909 - 1910 (Box-folder 129/2)
    - Correspondence, Glendive-Mandan line (Montana-SD), 1909 - 1910 (Box-folder 129/3)
    - Correspondence, Glendive Montana, 1909 - 1910 (Box-folder 129/4)
    - Correspondence, Helena-Billings-Miles City line (Montana), 1940 - 1949 (Box-folder 129/5)
    - Correspondence, Missoula-Miles City line (Montana), 1940 - 1949 (Box-folder 129/6)
    - Correspondence, Montana towns, 1940 - 1949 (Box-folder 129/7)
    - Correspondence, Circle-Poplar-Savage line Montana, 1940 - 1949 (Box-folder 130/1)
    - Correspondence, Montana towns, 1940 - 1959 (Box-folder 130/2)
    - Correspondence, Montana towns, 1940 - 1959 (Box-folder 130/3)
    - Correspondence, Montana towns, 1940 - 1959 (Box-folder 130/4)
    - Correspondence, Montana towns, 1940 - 1959 (Box-folder 130/5)
    - Correspondence, Billings-Helena line Montana, 1949 - 1950 (Box-folder 130/6)
    - Correspondence, Montana stations, 1950 - 1959 (Box-folder 130/7)
    - Correspondence, Miles City, Montana, 1950 - 1959 (Box-folder 131/1)
    - Correspondence, Billings, Montana, 1950 - 1959 (Box-folder 131/2)
    - Correspondence, Billings, Montana, 1950 - 1959 (Box-folder 131/3)
    - Correspondence, Red Lodge-Billings line, Montana, 1950 - 1959 (Box-folder 131/4)
    - Correspondence, Billings-Ralpelje line, Montana, 1950 - 1959 (Box-folder 131/5)
    - Correspondence, Glendive-Helena line, Montana, 1950 - 1959 (Box-folder 131/6)
    - Correspondence, Montana stations, 1950 - 1959 (Box-folder 132/1)
    - Correspondence, Montana stations, 1950 - 1959 (Box-folder 132/2)
    - Correspondence, Montana stations, 1950 - 1959 (Box-folder 132/3)
    - Correspondence, Montana stations, 1950 - 1959 (Box-folder 132/4)
    - Correspondence, Montana stations, 1950 - 1959 (Box-folder 132/5)
    - Correspondence, Colstrip, Montana, 1950 - 1959 (Box-folder 133/1)
    - Correspondence, Glendive, Montana, 1950 - 1959 (Box-folder 133/2)
    - Correspondence, Springdale-Wilsall line, Montana, 1950 - 1959 (Box-folder 133/3)
    - Correspondence, Billings, Montana, 1950 - 1959 (Box-folder 133/4)
    - Correspondence, Montana stations, 1950 - 1959 (Box-folder 133/5)
    - Correspondence, Montana stations, 1950 - 1959 (Box-folder 134/1)
    - Correspondence, Billings, Montana, 1950 - 1959 (Box-folder 134/2)
    - Correspondence, Billings, Montana, 1950 - 1959 (Box-folder 134/3)
    - Correspondence, Billings, Montana, 1950 - 1959 (Box-folder 134/4)
    - Correspondence, Billings, Montana, 1950 - 1959 (Box-folder 134/5)
    - Correspondence, Billings, Montana, 1950 - 1959 (Box-folder 135/1)
    - Correspondence, Billings, Montana, 1950 - 1959 (Box-folder 135/2)
    - Correspondence, Billings, Montana, 1950 - 1959 (Box-folder 135/3)
    - Correspondence, Billings, Montana, 1950 - 1959 (Box-folder 135/4)
    - Correspondence, Billings, Montana, 1950 - 1959 (Box-folder 135/5)
    - Correspondence, Billings, Montana, 1950 - 1959 (Box-folder 136/1)
    - Correspondence, Billings, Montana, 1950 - 1959 (Box-folder 136/2)
    - Correspondence, Billings, Montana, 1950 - 1959 (Box-folder 136/3)
    - Correspondence, Billings, Montana, 1950 - 1959 (Box-folder 136/4)
    - Correspondence, Forsyth, Montana, 1950 - 1959 (Box-folder 137/1)
    - Correspondence, Forsyth, Montana, 1950 - 1959 (Box-folder 137/2)
    - Correspondence, Billings, Montana, 1950 - 1959 (Box-folder 137/3)
    - Correspondence, Laurel-Joliet line, Montana, 1950 - 1959 (Box-folder 137/4)
    - Correspondence, Joliet, Montana, 1950 - 1959 (Box-folder 137/5)
    - Correspondence, Helena-Huntley line, Montana, 1950 - 1959 (Box-folder 137/6)
    - Correspondence, Montana stations, 1950 - 1959 (Box-folder 138/1)
    - Correspondence, Big Timber, Montana, 1950 - 1959 (Box-folder 138/2)
    - Correspondence, Billings-Missoula line, Montana, 1950 - 1959 (Box-folder 138/3)
    - Correspondence, Miles City, Montana, 1950 - 1959 (Box-folder 138/4)
    - Correspondence, Laurel-Custer line, Montana, 1950 - 1959 (Box-folder 138/5)
    - Correspondence, Montana stations, 1950 - 1959 (Box-folder 138/6)
    - Correspondence, Bridger, Montana, 1950 - 1959 (Box-folder 139/1)
    - Correspondence, Red Lodge, Montana, 1950 - 1959 (Box-folder 139/2)
    - Correspondence, Columbus, Montana, 1950 - 1959 (Box-folder 139/3)
    - Reports, Missoula, Montana, 1950 - 1959 (Box-folder 139/4)
    - Reports, Montana Business, 1950 - 1959 (Box-folder 139/5)
    - Montana Reports and Correspondence, 1890 (Box-folder 139/6)
    - Montana Financial Records, Reports, and Contracts, 1909 (Box-folder 140/1)
    - Montana Financial Records, Reports, and Contracts, 1909 (Box-folder 140/2)
    - Montana Financial Records, Reports, and Contracts, 1910 (Box-folder 140/3)
    - Montana Financial and Legal Records, Reports, and Contracts - Stampede Tunnel, 1885 (Box-folder 140/4)
    - General Correspondence, Blossbury Ventilating Plant, 1932 (Box-folder 140/5)
    - General Correspondence, Avon, Montana, 1932 (Box-folder 140/6)
    - General Correspondence, Drummond, Montana, 1931 (Box-folder 140/7)
    - General Correspondence, Drummond, Montana, 1934 (Box-folder 140/8)
    - General Correspondence, Missoula, Montana, 1932 (Box-folder 140/9)
    - General Correspondence, Drummond, Montana - Highway crossing, 1934 (Box-folder 140/10)
    - General Correspondence, Missoula, Montana - Missoula Mercantile Company, 1934 (Box-folder 140/11)
    - General Correspondence, Garrison, Montana, 1932 (Box-folder 140/12)
    - General Correspondence, Garrison, Montana, 1933 (Box-folder 140/13)
    - General Correspondence, Garrison, Montana, 1933 (Box-folder 140/14)
    - General Correspondence, Gold Creek, Montana, 1934 (Box-folder 140/15)
    - General Correspondence, Missoula Depot grounds and businesses, 1931 - 1934 (Box-folder 140/16)
    - General Correspondence, Missoula Freight House, 1931 (Box-folder 140/17)
    - General Correspondence, Missoula Station Lighting, 1932 (Box-folder 140/18)
    - General Correspondence, Missoula Lunch Room, 1934 (Box-folder 140/19)
    - General Correspondence, Missoula - Rate of Pay and Duties, 1934 (Box-folder 140/20)
    - General Correspondence, Silver Bow County, Montana, 1932 (Box-folder 140/21)
    - Appraisal report, Bearmouth, Montana, 1966 (Box-folder 141/1)
    - Correspondence with the Dakota Division, 1903 (Box-folder 142/1)
    - Correspondence with the Dakota Division, 1905 (Box-folder 142/2)
    - Correspondence with the Dakota Division, 1906 (Box-folder 142/3)
    - Correspondence with the Dakota Division, 1906 (Box-folder 142/4)
    - Correspondence with the Dakota Division, 1908 - 1910 (Box-folder 142/5)
    - Dining Car Receipts, Paradise, Montana, 1964-01 - 1964-06 (Box-folder 143/1)
    - Dining Car Receipts, Paradise, Montana, 1964-07 - 1964-12 (Box-folder 143/2)
    - Dining Car Receipts, Helena, Montana, 1964-04 - 1964-07 (Box-folder 143/3)
    - Dining Car Receipts, Helena, Montana, 1964-08 - 1964-12 (Box-folder 143/4)
    - Dining Car Receipts, Missoula, Montana, 1964 (Box-folder 144/1)
    - Dining Car Receipts, Fargo, North Dakota, 1964-01 - 1964-04 (Box-folder 144/2)
    - Dining Car Receipts, Fargo, North Dakota, 1964-05 - 1964-08 (Box-folder 144/3)
    - Dining Car Receipts, Fargo, North Dakota, 1964-09 - 1964-12 (Box-folder 144/4)
    - Dining car pay deduction receipts, 1964 (Box-folder 145A/1)
    - Meal Books, Dining car receipts, 1964-08 (Box-folder 145A/2)
    - Meal Books, Dining car receipts, 1964-09 (Box-folder 145A/3)
    - Meal Books, Dining car receipts, 1964-10 (Box-folder 145A/4)
    - Meal Books, Dining car receipts, 1964-11 (Box-folder 145A/5)
    - Meal Books, Dining car receipts, 1964-12 (Box-folder 145A/6)
    - General Correspondence, Bitterroot Branch, 1918 - 1960 (Box-folder 145B/1)
    - General Correspondence, Bitterroot Branch, 1918 - 1960 (Box-folder 145B/2)
    - General Correspondence, Bitterroot Branch, 1918 - 1960 (Box-folder 145B/3)
    - General Correspondence, Bitterroot Branch, 1918 - 1960 (Box-folder 145B/4)
    - General Correspondence, Bitterroot Branch, 1918 - 1960 (Box-folder 145B/5)
    - Blueprints, Bitterroot Branch, undated (Box-folder 145B/6)
    - General Correspondence, Couer d'Alene Branch, 1908 - 1957 (Box-folder 145B/7)
    - General Correspondence, Livingston Branch, 1932 - 1956 (Box-folder 145B/8)
    - General Correspondence, Livingston Branch, 1932 - 1956 (Box-folder 145C/1)
    - General Correspondence, Livingston Branch, 1932 - 1956 (Box-folder 145C/2)
    - General Correspondence, Livingston-Garrison Branch, 1931 - 1939 (Box-folder 145C/3)
    - General Correspondence, Livingston-Garrison Branch, 1940 - 1944 (Box-folder 145D/1)
    - General Correspondence, Livingston-Garrison Branch, 1945 (Box-folder 145D/2)
    - General Correspondence, Livingston-Garrison Branch, 1945 (Box-folder 145D/3)
    - General Correspondence, Livingston-Garrison Branch, 1946 - 1948 (Box-folder 145D/4)
    - General Correspondence, Livingston-Garrison Branch, 1949 (Box-folder 145D/5)
    - General Correspondence, Livingston-Garrison Branch, 1949 (Box-folder 145D/6)
    - General Correspondence, Livingston-Garrison Branch, 1950 - 1952 (Box-folder 145E/1)
    - General Correspondence, Livingston-Garrison Branch, 1953 - 1954 (Box-folder 145E/2)
    - General Correspondence, Livingston-Garrison Branch, 1955 (Box-folder 145E/3)
    - General Correspondence, Livingston-Garrison Branch, Butte, Montana, 1954 (Box-folder 145E/4)
    - General Correspondence, Livingston-Garrison Branch, Butte, Montana, 1954 (Box-folder 145E/5)
    - General Correspondence, Livingston-Garrison Branch, Butte, Montana, 1955 (Box-folder 145F/1)
    - General Correspondence, Livingston-Garrison Branch, Butte, Montana, 1955 (Box-folder 145F/2)
    - General Correspondence, Livingston-Garrison Branch, Butte, Montana, 1955 (Box-folder 145F/3)
    - General Correspondence, Livingston-Garrison Branch, Butte, Montana, 1956 (Box-folder 145F/4)
    - General Correspondence, Livingston-Garrison Branch, Butte, Montana, undated (Box-folder 145F/5)
    - General Correspondence, Livingston-Garrison Branch, 1957 - 1959 (Box-folder 145G/1)
    - General Correspondence, Livingston-Garrison Branch, Concrete Plant in East Helena, undated (Box-folder 145G/2)
    - General Correspondence, Livingston-Garrison Branch, Concrete Plant in East Helena, undated (Box-folder 145G/3)
    - General Correspondence, Livingston-Garrison Branch, 1961 - 1967 (Box-folder 145G/4)
    - General Correspondence, Missoula Branch, 1918 - 1935 (Box-folder 145G/5)
    - General Correspondence, Missoula Branch, 1936 - 1939 (Box-folder 145H/1)
    - General Correspondence, Missoula Branch, 1940 - 1945 (Box-folder 145H/2)
    - General Correspondence, Missoula Branch, 1946 (Box-folder 145H/3)
    - General Correspondence, Missoula Branch, 1947 (Box-folder 145H/4)
    - General Correspondence, Missoula Branch, 1948 - 1949 (Box-folder 145H/5)
    - General Correspondence, Missoula Branch, 1950 (Box-folder 145I/1)
    - General Correspondence, Missoula Branch, 1951 (Box-folder 145I/2)
    - General Correspondence, Missoula Branch, 1952 (Box-folder 145I/3)
    - General Correspondence, Missoula Branch, 1953 (Box-folder 145I/4)
    - General Correspondence, Missoula Branch, 1954 (Box-folder 145I/5)
    - General Correspondence, Missoula Branch, 1955 (Box-folder 145J/1)
    - General Correspondence, Missoula Branch, 1955 (Box-folder 145J/2)
    - General Correspondence, Missoula Branch, 1955 (Box-folder 145J/3)
    - General Correspondence, Missoula Branch, 1956 (Box-folder 145K/1)
    - General Correspondence, Missoula Branch, 1956 (Box-folder 145K/2)
    - General Correspondence, Missoula Branch, 1957 (Box-folder 145K/3)
    - General Correspondence, Missoula Branch, 1958 (Box-folder 145K/4)
    - General Correspondence, Missoula Branch, 1959 (Box-folder 145K/5)
    - General Correspondence, Missoula Branch, 1960 (Box-folder 145K/6)
    - General Correspondence, Missoula Branch, 1961 - 1967 (Box-folder 145L/1)
    - General Correspondence, Missoula Branch, Paving Missoula Stockyard, 1946 - 1947 (Box-folder 145L/2)
    - Blueprints, Bitterroot Branch, undated (Box-folder 145L/3)
    - Blueprints, Bitterroot Branch, undated (Box-folder 145L/4)
    - Blueprints, Bitterroot Branch, undated (Box-folder 145L/5)
    - Blueprints, Bitterroot Branch, undated (Box-folder 145L/6)
    - Blueprints and Drawings, Livingston Branch, 1932 - 1956 (Box-folder 145M/1)
    - Blueprints and Drawings, Livingston Branch, 1932 - 1956 (Box-folder 145M/2)
    - Blueprints and Drawings, Livingston Branch, 1932 - 1956 (Box-folder 145M/3)
    - Blueprints and Drawings, Livingston Branch, 1932 - 1956 (Box-folder 145M/4)
    - Blueprints, Livingston Branch, undated (Box-folder 145N/1)
    - Blueprints, Livingston Branch, undated (Box-folder 145N/2)
    - Blueprints, Livingston Branch, undated (Box-folder 145N/3)
    - Blueprints, Livingston-Garrison Branch, undated (Box-folder 145O/1)
    - Blueprints, Livingston-Garrison Branch, undated (Box-folder 145O/2)
    - Blueprints, Livingston-Garrison Branch, undated (Box-folder 145O/3)
    - Blueprints, Missoula Branch, undated (Box-folder 145O/4)
    - Blueprints, Missoula Branch, undated (Box-folder 145O/5)
    - Blueprints, Missoula Branch, undated (Box-folder 145P/1)
    - Blueprints, Missoula Branch, undated (Box-folder 145P/2)
    - Blueprints, Missoula Branch, undated (Box-folder 145P/3)
    - Blueprints, Missoula Branch, undated (Box-folder 145P/4)
    - Blueprints, Missoula Branch, Missoula Stockyard, undated (Box-folder 145P/5)
    - Blueprints, Missoula Branch, Cross Sections, undated (Box-folder 145P/6)
    - Blueprints, Missoula Branch, Paving Missoula Stockyard, 1947 (Box-folder 145P/7)
    - Blueprints, Missoula Branch, undated (Box-folder 145P/8)
    - Blueprints, Missoula Branch, undated (Box-folder 145Q/1)
    - Blueprints, Missoula Branch, undated (Box-folder 145Q/2)
    - Blueprints, Missoula Branch, undated (Box-folder 145Q/3)
    - Blueprints, Missoula Branch, undated (Box-folder 145Q/4)
    - Blueprints, Missoula Branch, undated (Box-folder 145R/1)
    - Blueprints, Missoula Branch, undated (Box-folder 145R/2)
    - Blueprints, Missoula Branch, undated (Box-folder 145R/3)
    - Blueprints, Missoula Branch, undated (Box-folder 145R/4)
    - Blueprints, Missoula Branch, undated (Box-folder 145R/5)
    - Blueprints, Missoula Branch, undated (Box-folder 145S/1)
    - Blueprints, Missoula Branch, undated (Box-folder 145S/2)
    - Blueprints, Missoula Branch, undated (Box-folder 145S/3)
    - Blueprints, Missoula Branch, undated (Box-folder 145S/4)
    - Blueprints, Missoula Branch, undated (Box-folder 145T/1)
    - Blueprints, Missoula Branch, undated (Box-folder 145T/2)
    - Blueprints, Missoula Branch, undated (Box-folder 145T/3)
  - Yellowstone Division (Montana/Idaho), 1881-1953; Series X; 0.75 linear feet
    This series includes construction documents generated by the Yellowstone (River) Division of the Northern Pacific Railroad, operating primarily in southeastern Montana. These records consist of construction/repair project correspondence and financial records. Financial records include details of materials used and projected costs. This series also includes a single folder of materials regarding the Shields River Branch of the NPRR.
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Billings, Montana, 1891-1892 (Box-volume 146/210)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Charles A. Dewar, 1883-1885 (Box-volume 146/211)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, 1889-1891 (Box-volume 146/212)
    - Financial Records, Construction Department, 1882-1883 (Box-volume 146/213)
    - Financial Records, Bridge Records, 1881 (Box-volume 147/214)
    - Shields River Branch (Montana), 1952-1953 (Box-folder 147/1)
  - General Oregon/Washington, 1880-1910; Series XI; 28.0 linear feet
    This series contains general correspondence, blueprints, and financial records (including station reports and contracts) from the Washington and Oregon lines of the NPRR. Correspondence records primarily consist of intenal documents detailing administrative policies, construction projects, land purchases, and supply requests as well as extensive exchanges with construction subcontractors, unaffiliated lines, and station supply vendors. Within the financial records are abstracts, vouchers, payroll documents, and correspondence. These financial records compliment the correspondence files in detailing construction project logistics, personnel actions, and agreements with subcontractors and vendors. The bound volumes of construction financial records provide extensive details on materials used, local and imported resources, work force structures, and projected costs for alternate approaches.
    - General Correspondence, Oregon, 1882 - 1884 (Box-folder 148/1)
    - General Correspondence, Washington and Oregon, 1882 - 1887 (Box-folder 148/2)
    - General Correspondence, Washington and Oregon, 1884 - 1886 (Box-folder 148/3)
    - General Correspondence, Washington and Oregon, 1884 - 1885 (Box-folder 149/1)
    - General Correspondence, Washington and Oregon, 1885 - 1886 (Box-volume 149/2)